tacobell.com 2016-06-17

# Privacy Policy - Taco Bell

Our Policy describes how we treat personal information on the websites where it is located. This includes [fourthmeal.com](http://www.fourthmeal.com/), [tacobellforteens.org](http://www.tacobellforteens.org/), and [feedthebeat.com](http://www.feedthebeat.com/), [indiegamegarage.com](http://www.indiegamegarage.com/). This includes mobile versions of our websites. It also applies to our mobile and social media apps.

This policy does not apply to the websites and practices of Yum! Brands, Inc. or other members of Yum! Brands like Pizza Hut or KFC. It also does not apply to the practices of Yum Brands subsidiaries or other affiliates. This policy also does not describe the activities of any Taco Bell franchisees.

## Hey Taco Bell, what information do you collect?

#### We Collect Contact information

For example, we might collect your name and street address if you register on our site. We might also collect your phone number or email address.

#### We collect payment information

For example, we collect your gift card number to check your balance. We may also collect your credit card information if you make a purchase.

#### We collect information you submit or post

We collect the information you share, post or provide on our websites and apps. We also collect information about your transactions on our apps. For example, if you place an order, we collect information about your order. This might include the items purchased or the payment and billing information. It might also include the date and amount of the purchase.

#### We Collect Demographic Information

We may collect information like your gender and age. We may also collect your zip code. We may also collect information about a Taco Bell you visited. We might collect this when you give us customer feedback.

#### We collect other information

If you use our website, we may collect IP addresses and information about the browser you’re using. We might look at what site you came from, or what site you visit when you leave us. If you use our mobile app, we may collect your GPS location or, as permitted, address book information and photos. We might also collect device identifiers. We might look at how often you use the app and where you downloaded it. We might also collect other information we describe to you.

## And how do you collect it?

#### We collect information directly from you

For example, if you register with us or enter a sweepstakes. We also collect information if you make a purchase or fill out an online survey.

#### We collect information from you passively

We use tracking tools like browser cookies and web beacons. We also collect information from our mobile apps. We collect information about users over time when you use our websites and apps. We may have third parties collect personal information this way. Learn more about these tools and how you can control them, here.

#### We get information about you from third parties

For example, our business partners may give us information about you. Social media platforms may also give us information about you.

#### We might combine information

For example, we may combine information that we have collected offline with information we collect online. Or we may combine information we get from a third party with information we already have.

## How do you use the info?

#### We use information to respond to your requests or questions

For example, we might use your information to respond to your customer feedback. We may use your friend’s email address if you use our send-a-friend feature. We may also use your information to fulfill your order.

#### We use information to improve our products and services

We may use your information to make our website and products better. We might use your information to customize your experience with us. We may combine information we get from you with information about you we get from third parties.

#### We use information for security purposes

We may use information to protect our company, our customers, and our websites.

#### We use information for marketing purposes

For example, we might send you information about new products and special offers. We might also use your information to serve you ads about products and offers. We might tell you about new features or updates. These might be third party offers or products we think you might find interesting. If you register with us, we’ll enroll you in our email newsletter. To learn about your choices for these communications, read the choices section below.

#### We use information to communicate with you

For example, we will communicate with you about your account or our relationship. We may contact you about your account or feedback. We might also contact you about this Policy or our website Terms. We may use push notifications on our mobile apps.

#### We use information to talk to parents or guardians to get permission

We may use contact information to get permission from parents for children who want to use our site.

#### We use information as otherwise permitted by law

## What about sharing with third parties?

#### We may share information within the Yum! Brand family of companies

This includes KFC, Pizza Hut, WingStreet, and Yum Restaurants International. This also includes future subsidiaries or affiliates. For a full list visit [yum.com/brands](http://www.yum.com/brands).

#### We may share information with third parties who perform services on our behalf

For example, we share information with vendors who send emails for us. We may also share information with companies that operate our websites or run a promotion.

#### We may share information with our business partners

For example, we will share information with third parties who co-sponsor a promotion or operate our “store finder” service. These partners may send you information about events and products by mail or email. 

#### We may share information if we think we have to in order to comply with the law or to protect ourselves.

For example, we will share information to respond to a court order or subpoena. We may share it if a government agency or investigatory body requests. We might share information when we are investigating potential fraud. This might include fraud we think has happened during a sweepstakes or promotion. Or we may share your information if you are the winner of a sweepstakes or other contest with anyone who requests a winner’s list.

#### We may share information with any successor to all or part of our business

For example, if part of our business was sold we may give our customer list as part of that transaction.

#### We may share information for other reasons we may describe to you

## Do I have certain choices about sharing and marketing practices?

#### You can opt out of receiving our marketing emails

To stop receiving our promotional emails, email us at unsubscribe@tacobell.com or follow the instructions in any promotional message you get from us. Even if you opt out of getting marketing messages, we will still send you messages about your questions and purchases.

#### You can control if we share information with third parties for their marketing purposes

To opt out of having us share your information with third parties for their promotional purposes, click here[](http://www.tacobell.com/legal-notices/about-our-ads). Your opt-out will be effective until you revoke it. Your opt-out will only affect the future sharing of information and will not be retroactive.

#### You can control certain cookies and tracking tools

To learn how to manage how we – and our vendors – use cookies and other tracking tools, and to read our Do Not Track policy, please click here.

#### You can control tools on your mobile devices

For example, you can turn off the GPS locator or push notifications on your phone. To modify the push notifications you get from our app, you can alter your preferences in your profile.

## What does the policy have to say about children?

Our sites and apps are meant for adults. We do not knowingly collect personally identifiable information from children under 13 without permission from a parent or guardian. If you are a parent or legal guardian and think your child under 13 has given us information, you can email us. You can also write to us at the address listed at the end of this policy. Please mark your inquiries “COPPA Information Request.”

Parents, you can learn more about how to protect children's privacy on-line [here](http://www.consumer.ftc.gov/articles/0031-protecting-your-childs-privacy-online).

## How safe is my info?

We use standard security measures. Keep in mind that the Internet is never 100% secure because there are always people out there who want to ruin it for everyone. We cannot promise that your use of our sites and apps will be completely safe. We encourage you to use caution when using the Internet. This includes not sharing your passwords.

We keep personal information as long as it is necessary or relevant for the practices described in this Policy. We also keep information as otherwise required by law.

## We store information in the United States

If you live outside of the United States, you understand and agree that we may transfer your information to the United States. Our sites and apps are subject to U.S. laws.

## We may link to other sites or have third party services on our site we don’t control

If you click on a link to a third party site, you will be taken to websites or platforms we do not control. This policy does not apply to the privacy practices of that website or platform. Read the privacy policy of other websites and platforms carefully. We are not responsible for these third party practices.

Our site may also serve third party content that contains its own cookies or tracking technologies. To learn more, click here. We do not control the use of those technologies.

## Feel free to contact us if you have more questions

If you have any questions about this Policy, please email us at webmaster@tacobell.com.

You can also write to us or call at:  
Taco Bell Corp.  
1 Glen Bell Way  
Irvine, CA 92618  
Phone: (949) 863-4000

## Stay tuned for updates

From time to time we may change our privacy policies. We will notify you of any material changes to our Policy as required by law. We will also post an updated copy on our website. Please check our site periodically for updates.

© 2015 Taco Bell Corp. All rights reserved.

Effective as of 7/11/2006, last updated September 21, 2015
